<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <title>No More Cable TV</title>
  <slug>no-more-cable-tv</slug>
  <author>demo</author>
  <pubDate>2011-08-21 03:21:46</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2016-11-14 03:35:43</lastModified>
  <excerpt>For months, I have been thinking about canceling my television cable subscription.  Now, I finally did it and I couldn’t be happier about it.</excerpt>
  <content>&lt;p style="border:0;font-family:&amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif;font-size:15px;margin-bottom:1.625em;outline:0;padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0;vertical-align:baseline;color:rgb(55,55,55)"&gt;For months, I have been thinking about canceling my television cable subscription.  Now, I finally did it and I couldn’t be happier about it.  I have nothing against cable companies.  They offer a service for a fee that for the most part is affordable and convenient – for most people; not for me.  My reason for wanting to get rid of cable TV was twofold: I wanted to cut down on watching TV, and couldn’t justify the cost benefit ratio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border:0;font-family:&amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif;font-size:15px;margin-bottom:1.625em;outline:0;padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0;vertical-align:baseline;color:rgb(55,55,55)"&gt;I’m a news junkie – mostly political news – and can spend hours a day watching nothing but news channels such as Fox, CNN, and PBS – and the Sunday News/Political commentary shows on the alphabet channels (ABC, NBC, and CBS).  And for the most part that was all I ever watched on a regular basis; nothing else.  No movies, no TV programs – well, maybe a Seinfeld rerun once in a while – no sports, nothing.  So, in my mind paying $70.00 a month for basic cable subscription to watch news over and over, news that I could probably read on the internet was not worth it and was wasting my time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border:0;font-family:&amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif;font-size:15px;margin-bottom:1.625em;outline:0;padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0;vertical-align:baseline;color:rgb(55,55,55)"&gt;Now I have a device called Roku (&lt;a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130724015551/http://www.roku.com/" style="border:0;font-family:inherit;font-style:inherit;font-weight:inherit;margin:0;outline:0;padding:0;vertical-align:baseline;color:rgb(25,130,209)"&gt;http://www.roku.com&lt;/a&gt; ).  No more paying for 100+ channels I’m not interested in.  Currently I only pay $8.00 a month for a Netflix subscription that streams movies and other videos via my Roku.  I justify this monthly subscription because I was spending that much renting $1.00 movies at Red Box kiosks and other places.  Now I have lot’s more to choose from and I don’t pay late fees.  I also use Roku to stream music via Pandora, and use it to watch free technology channels such as TWiT.tv, YUI Theater, CNET, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border:0;font-family:&amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif;font-size:15px;margin-bottom:1.625em;outline:0;padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0;vertical-align:baseline;color:rgb(55,55,55)"&gt;Before I decided to go with Roku I did some research and found that there are many similar devices.  After spending many hours comparing features and reading reviews I decided to go ahead and spend $99.99 for the high end version – and I’m glad I did.  This device was the only one that supported the 1080p HD quality via an HDMI cable, and had a USB port.  That was two months ago.  Today there are newer versions called ROKU 2 with more features and for the same prices.  The most expensive device is still $99.99 but it now includes a free full edition of Angry Birds and it has an Ethernet port.  Now you can get one that supports the 1080p HD for $79.99.  Maybe I’ll buy a new one for the bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border:0;font-family:&amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif;font-size:15px;margin-bottom:1.625em;outline:0;padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0;vertical-align:baseline;color:rgb(55,55,55)"&gt;In summary: I’m not watching as much news and political commentaries as before – a good thing.  And I’m not spending $70.00 a month on cable TV.  I really miss FOX and CNN, but now I get to spend more time doing other things such as reading, working on my websites, and blogging.  Now, if I could just stop playing Angry Birds….&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>true</ispublished>
  <categories>
    <category>Cable TV</category>
    <category>TV</category>
    <category>Roku</category>
    <category>Personal</category>
    <category>Opinion</category>
  </categories>
  <comments></comments>
</post>