<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <title>Small Things That Make a Difference</title>
  <slug>small-things-that-make-a-difference</slug>
  <author>abelgaxiola</author>
  <pubDate>2014-01-30 04:34:01</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-01-30 04:34:01</lastModified>
  <excerpt>For years now my wife has made it a point to include small notes with my lunch. She does this randomly and I never know when I’ll be opening my lunch box and find one of these notes.</excerpt>
  <content>&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;For years now my wife has made it a point to include small notes with my lunch. She does this randomly and I never know when I’ll be opening my lunch box and find one of these notes. The stationary she uses is nothing special, just a regular piece of paper or one of those Post-It notes. She handwrites the message and writes wishing me good luck or thanking me for something, and most of the time she will end the message saying that she loves me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;The point is that I’m always surprised when I find one of the notes and it always turns my day into a better day and make me feel really good about myself and my relationship with my wife. I don’t know if I can say the same about myself. I hope that some of the things I do are also received by her in the same manner – I just don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;I do know this: those little notes in my lunch box sure make me feel good.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>true</ispublished>
  <categories>
    <category>Personal</category>
    <category>Opinion</category>
    <category>Family</category>
  </categories>
  <comments></comments>
</post>