<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <title>On your marks, get set…</title>
  <slug>on-your-marks-get-set…</slug>
  <author>abelgaxiola</author>
  <pubDate>2012-05-15 04:01:12</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2012-05-15 04:01:12</lastModified>
  <excerpt>Yearly family reunion for Familia Gaxiola.</excerpt>
  <content>&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;If we don’t count today (May 15, 2012) there are only ten days left for the “Tour de Kino” bike ride and Gaxiola family reunion. And counting today, there are only ten days left for the getting together at the “Casa de la Abuelita” where we will enjoy some valuable family time with the early arrivals from out-of-town and our family in Hermosillo. The time that I spend with those I love and love me is time that I will cherish forever. The bike ride (100 Km) is a different story: I really don’t know why I do it – I just do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;I still don’t know for sure why I agree to participate in the 100k bike ride – but I’m glad I do. I suppose the fact that I’m participating in an event that includes other members of the family has a lot to do with it. And, without a doubt, the fact that preparing for the ride has its health benefits is something that makes it worth the effort. Besides, how can I not participate in an event where people that I admire such as Pancho Cuamea, brothers, uncles, cousins, and friends are riding their bikes? I know it’s going to be hard, and painful, and… but I must suffer with them. Besides: it’s therapy – just what the doctor ordered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;See you there…&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>true</ispublished>
  <categories>
    <category>Personal</category>
    <category>Family</category>
    <category>Gaxiola</category>
  </categories>
  <comments></comments>
</post>