<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <title>2011 Resolution Follow Up</title>
  <slug>2011-resolution-follow-up</slug>
  <author>abelgaxiola</author>
  <pubDate>2011-02-13 04:33:15</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2011-02-13 04:36:02</lastModified>
  <excerpt>One of my three part New Year’s resolution was to get familiar with ASP.NET MVC.  I have for the past month been working on my spare time migrating a website from standard ASP.NET to the MVC architecture using MVC2.</excerpt>
  <content>&lt;p style="border:0;font-family:&amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif;font-size:15px;margin-bottom:1.625em;outline:0;padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0;vertical-align:baseline;color:rgb(55,55,55)"&gt;One of my three part New Year’s resolution was to get familiar with ASP.NET MVC.  I have for the past month been working on my spare time migrating a website from standard ASP.NET to the MVC architecture using MVC2.  The process has been slow but I feel that I’ve learned a lot in the process.  In the meantime, while working on the website migration a few other technologies that I’ve been reading about (mostly in blogs) were officially released; they were: ASP.NET MVC3, WebMatrix, and Orchard, to name a few.  Since my resolution is mostly about staying up-to-date with technology (mostly for the MS stack since that is where I spend most of my time) I decided to take a look at what the noise was about.  If you are interested in some of the technologies I just mentioned take a look at the following blog entry by Scott Gu: &lt;font color="#1982d1" face="inherit"&gt;&lt;span style="border-style: initial; border-color: initial; border-image: initial; font-size: 15px; font-style: inherit; font-weight: inherit; outline-color: initial; outline-style: initial;"&gt;&lt;a href="http://weblogs.asp.net/scottgu/archive/2011/01/13/announcing-release-of-asp-net-mvc-3-iis-express-sql-ce-4-web-farm-framework-orchard-webmatrix.aspx"&gt;Blog Entry for January 13&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border:0;font-family:&amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif;font-size:15px;margin-bottom:1.625em;outline:0;padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0;vertical-align:baseline;color:rgb(55,55,55)"&gt;Since one of the technologies I have been learning is MVC2 I decided to move forward and take a look at MVC3 and have to say that it is impressive.  I was also impressed with WebMatrix and how easy it is to create and publish some pretty complex sites, as well as some simple ones.  Orchard impressed me the most and I created a sample website on my workstation that I felt had promise; but when it was published it was a different story (my hosting provider is godaddy).  Accessing and navigating the site was slower than acceptable and so I took it off after spending hours trying to make it load faster  — too bad because I was hoping to use it for one of my sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border:0;font-family:&amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;,Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif;font-size:15px;margin-bottom:1.625em;outline:0;padding-top:0;padding-bottom:0;vertical-align:baseline;color:rgb(55,55,55)"&gt;In the mean time I have been playing with MVC3 and have published a site built using VS 2010’s MVC3 website template.  I created a sandbox site that I intend to use for testing and trying new technologies. Right now there is only one site but I intend to use it for other experiments.  I will share my successes as well as my failures in this blog, and maybe my experiences will be of benefit to someone else.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>true</ispublished>
  <categories>
    <category>Personal</category>
  </categories>
  <comments></comments>
</post>