<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <title>The Third Pillar</title>
  <slug>the-third-pillar</slug>
  <author>abelgaxiola</author>
  <pubDate>2011-08-16 05:26:56</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2011-08-16 05:26:56</lastModified>
  <excerpt>I have a problem: when I said in my New Year’s resolution that I was going to improve my soul what I really meant is that I have resolved to become a better person. But how do I, or anyone else for that matter, measure the soul?</excerpt>
  <content>&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;I have a problem: when I said in my New Year’s resolution that I was going to improve my soul what I really meant is that I have resolved to become a better person. But how do I, or anyone else for that matter, measure the soul? Am I a better person now because I give to charities? Or am I simply doing it to fulfill a requirement that I set for myself, or am I doing it to satisfy my own selfish nature? Am I a better person because I haven’t lost my temper in the past 6 months? Or am I only suppressing my emotions and in the process creating a ticking time bomb that will go off with even greater force in the near future?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;What really makes a person a better human being? I think that one way of measuring personal growth is for us to remember our mistakes, learn from our mistakes, and stop committing those same mistakes. I like to think that I have learned from my mistakes, and I know that I’m not committing many of my past mistakes; and wish I would have been able to say that I’m not committing any of my past mistakes. But, one thing I know for sure: I’m not what I want to be, and I’m not what I should be, but I’m sure not what I used to be. Why? Because nothing remains static: especially our personality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;Many times I hear people talk about someone they know and say “he is still the same”, or “he’ll never change”. Nothing could be further from the truth. Nothing is the same – ever. And we are always in a state of change – sometimes for the better, but unfortunately sometimes for the worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;I like to think that I’m changing for the better….&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>true</ispublished>
  <categories>
    <category>Personal</category>
  </categories>
  <comments></comments>
</post>