<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <title>Windows 8–The Good Parts</title>
  <slug>windows-8–the-good-parts</slug>
  <author>abelgaxiola</author>
  <pubDate>2012-07-15 04:42:42</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2012-07-15 04:44:32</lastModified>
  <excerpt>Now that W8 has finally been released to the general public I upgraded my laptop and removed my W7 operating system all together – and couldn’t be happier.</excerpt>
  <content>&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;A couple of months ago I installed Windows 8 beta on my three year old laptop that originally came preloaded with Windows Vista.  Having read many articles and blogs about W8 I wasn’t sold on the new operating system and decided to install it on a separate hard drive making my computer a double boot system and only booting into W8 once in a while to get acquainted with the OS.  Now that W8 has finally been released to the general public I upgraded my laptop and removed my W7 operating system all together – and couldn’t be happier.  Here’s why:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;1.  My system boots up from a cold start in less than half the time it used to take under W7.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;2.  When it's time to turn the computer off it shuts down faster.  And I mean a lot faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;3.  The start screen is much nicer to look at than the W7 desktop and the live titles are: Alive!  I just don’t know how else to describe them.  I get live and real time information on many of my W8 apps such as Bing, News, Weather, Travel, Stock Market, Calendar, Mail, and the People app hooks me up with messages and events from my Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, and Live accounts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;4.  There are keyboard shortcuts for almost everything I need to do.  Some of the most commonly used by me are: Win+F (search files), Win+W (search control panel), Win+X (administration options), Win+C (charms, time and date, and battery status).  Check out the following blog for plenty more: &lt;a title="http://www.hanselman.com/blog/Windows8ProductivityWhoMovedMyCheeseOhThereItIs.aspx" href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130208024753/http://www.hanselman.com/blog/Windows8ProductivityWhoMovedMyCheeseOhThereItIs.aspx"&gt;http://www.hanselman.com/blog/Windows8ProductivityWhoMovedMyCheeseOhThereItIs.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;5.  To run and application such as Word, Excel, FileZilla, or any other program all I have to do is start typing the name of the application and it will magically appear on the screen.  If the application’s name is highlighted all I have to do is press the enter key or click once with the mouse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;6.  If I don’t remember the name of the application all I have to do is use the keyboard shortcut of Win+Q and the screen is filled out with the name of all installed applications on my computer.  All nicely organized with much better looking icons than what the W7 Start Menu provides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;7.  All of my previously installed programs (remember that I upgraded from W7) still work, and they all feel more responsive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;8.  Some cool W8 apps: Mail, Calendar, People, Messaging, Netflix, SkyDrive, Skype, and Photos just to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;9.  And the best part: the cost of upgrading is only $39.99.  Don’t take my word for it.  Check it out: &lt;a title="http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows/buy" href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130208024753/http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows/buy"&gt;http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows/buy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color:rgb(0,0,0);font-family:&amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;;font-size:medium"&gt;See yea,&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>true</ispublished>
  <categories>
    <category>Technical</category>
    <category>Opinion</category>
    <category>Information</category>
  </categories>
  <comments></comments>
</post>