<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <title>El Tour de Kino 2012</title>
  <slug>el-tour-de-kino-2012</slug>
  <author>abelgaxiola</author>
  <pubDate>2012-06-11 04:05:23</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2012-06-11 04:05:23</lastModified>
  <excerpt>This year we got together like always: to enjoy some quality time with our family and friends. And also to honor a pillar of our great and beautiful family: Jesus Miguel Encinas Gaxiola (el Palle).</excerpt>
  <content>&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;Came and is now a memory in our minds and in our hearts. This year we got together like always: to enjoy some quality time with our family and friends. And also to honor a pillar of our great and beautiful family: Jesus Miguel Encinas Gaxiola (el Palle). The family reunion got started on Friday May 25&lt;span style="border: 0px; font-family: inherit; font-size: 10px; font-style: inherit; font-weight: inherit; margin: 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; height: 0px; line-height: 1; position: relative; bottom: 1ex;"&gt;th&lt;/span&gt; where members of the Encinas Gaxiola clan provided food and entertainment for all present. The food was great and the fellowship was even better; once again our family bonds were strengthened by the love and kindness of all present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;The next day we met at one of the local cemeteries where my grandparents, mother, and other family members are resting. This also has become a tradition and is now the starting place for the 100 km bicycle ride to Kino Bay. And so the Tour portion of the reunion got started. Not too many riders this year – eight in total – but the spirit to participate and compete was there. A little over three and a half hours later with only 200 meters remaining there was a sprint to the finish line and thanks to Jeff Farmer, Pancho Cuamea, and a good pair of legs I finished in first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;The entire day was a success. We had live music playing, plenty to eat and drink, and above all lots of love and kindness. We were all hoping that our beloved Palle would be able to make it to the reunion this year but unfortunately he was not feeling well and was not able to make it. Trophies were awarded to the first three places and a plaque recognizing Palle’s many years sponsoring and coordinating the family event was awarded to those members of his family that were present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;Sunday was a repeat: more live music, food and drink, and… plenty of love and kindness. Sunday is also the day when many have to leave and return to their homes. I know that many of those I said goodbye to I will not see again until next year – maybe and maybe not. I’m just glad I was able to see them and spend some time with them in fellowship this year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;&lt;a title="El Tour de Kino 2012 (Gaxiola Family Reunion)" href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130724015551/http://sdrv.ms/LU1Vv8" target="_blank" style="border: 0px; font-family: inherit; font-style: inherit; font-weight: inherit; margin: 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(25, 130, 209);"&gt;Pictures in SkyDrive&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;&lt;a title="Slide Show with &amp;quot;Viva Gaxiola&amp;quot; as background music" href="https://web.archive.org/web/20130724015551/http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Kyc4yolCIK8&amp;amp;list=UUgkaRWlB5OaCcoyNkHYEfLg&amp;amp;index=1&amp;amp;feature=plcp" target="_blank" style="border: 0px; font-family: inherit; font-style: inherit; font-weight: inherit; margin: 0px; outline: 0px; padding: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(25, 130, 209);"&gt;Picture slide show on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>true</ispublished>
  <categories>
    <category>Family</category>
    <category>Gaxiola</category>
    <category>Personal</category>
  </categories>
  <comments></comments>
</post>