<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <title>Staying Up-To-Date Is Hard Work (But Fun)</title>
  <slug>staying-up-to-date-is-hard-work-but-fun</slug>
  <author>abelgaxiola</author>
  <pubDate>2014-03-06 05:19:18</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-03-06 05:19:18</lastModified>
  <excerpt>So how does "Hard Work" === "Fun"?  The only way that I can explain it is by comparing it to the joy of ridding a bicycle 60 miles without stopping (something I do once a year at a family event): it's hard and painful but at the end the feeling of accomplishment makes it all worth the while.</excerpt>
  <content>&lt;p style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: &amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;; font-size: medium;"&gt;I was watching an online training video yesterday and found myself agreeing with everything that the presenter was saying.  The online video is provided by Pluralsight and the name of the course is "JavaScript the Good Parts" presented by Douglas Crockford.  Mr. Crockford makes it clear, at least to me, that writing software is hard work; and I couldn't agree more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: &amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;; font-size: medium;"&gt;Recently I been trying to update my skills to include modern web and mobile development.  Now, I say modern web because I've been doing web development for years but never fully understanding and applying the separation of concerns that are provided with HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript.  And, not until recently have I been concerned with my websites being responsive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: &amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;; font-size: medium;"&gt;Getting up to speed with the newest incarnation of these technologies and methodologies is taking me longer than anticipated, and it definitely takes work and effort to get it right.  But the satisfaction of getting it right once in a while or solving a problem makes it all worth the effort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); font-family: &amp;quot;Times New Roman&amp;quot;; font-size: medium;"&gt;So how does "Hard Work" === "Fun"?  The only way that I can explain it is by comparing it to the joy of ridding a bicycle 60 miles without stopping (something I do once a year at a family event): it's hard and painful but at the end the feeling of accomplishment makes it all worth the while.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>true</ispublished>
  <categories>
    <category>Technical</category>
    <category>Opinion</category>
  </categories>
  <comments></comments>
</post>