<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <title>Getting To Know Twitter (Again)</title>
  <slug>getting-to-know-twitter-again</slug>
  <author>abelgaxiola</author>
  <pubDate>2014-02-06 04:36:28</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-02-06 04:36:28</lastModified>
  <excerpt>I created a Twitter account on January 2010 and have to admit that I did not think much about the platform and thought even less about the fact that my posts have a 140 character restriction.  This year I decided to take a second look and see if I’m missing anything by mostly ignoring the platform.</excerpt>
  <content>&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;I created a Twitter account on January 2010 and have to admit that I did not think much about the platform and thought even less about the fact that my posts have a 140 character restriction.  This year I decided to take a second look and see if I’m missing anything by mostly ignoring the platform.  So what better way to get familiar with something but by using it and by doing some research.  And here is a summary of what I have found:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;Twitter is used by most major broadcasting companies in the world.  Those include television, cable, radio, news, etc.  The government and most of the politicians in the US have Twitter accounts.  Twitter has been instrumental in most of the recent popular movements, and it has become one of the preferred methods to disseminate information to members of the movement and to the world.  I don’t have the actual facts about this one but I’ll go out on a limb and say that most major corporations have Twitter accounts.  And without a doubt most public figures such as actors, singers, reporters, and the like, have accounts – some to their detriment.  Maybe all of these facts are obvious to most but I never really cared or paid any attention to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;So why am I talking about it today?  Because of something that happened in the last 24 hours: I posted a comment on Twitter that was retweeted to more than 103,900 twitter members, and it was favorited by six people that have a combined total of more than 700 followers.  So what does this mean?  It means that there is huge potential in the possibility of reaching beyond our inner circles.  And if that means anything to you, then you should consider getting to know Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="border: 0px; font-family: &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; margin-bottom: 1.625em; outline: 0px; padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; vertical-align: baseline; color: rgb(55, 55, 55);"&gt;If you do create a Twitter account don’t forget to ad @abelgaxiola and @familiagaxiola to your Following list.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>true</ispublished>
  <categories>
    <category>Technical</category>
    <category>Website</category>
    <category>Opinion</category>
  </categories>
  <comments></comments>
</post>